<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>armagan-karatosun on HomeAutomation.wiki</title><link>https://homeautomation.wiki/authors/armagan-karatosun/</link><description>Recent content in armagan-karatosun on HomeAutomation.wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://homeautomation.wiki/authors/armagan-karatosun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kubernetes L4 LoadBalancing with MetalLB</title><link>https://homeautomation.wiki/post/k8s-l4-lb-with-metallb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://homeautomation.wiki/post/k8s-l4-lb-with-metallb/</guid><description>Kubernetes L4 Load Balancing with MetalLB Although bare-metal installations of Kubernetes can support both L4 and L7 load-balancing, it comes without any pre-installed load-balancing support, especially on the L4 load balancing side, and expects for the administrator to bring his/her own desired choice.
I wanted to have this post dedicated to L4 load-balancing and how to provide it via MetalLB, but just for the sake to preserve the integrity of the topic, I want to give you a quick recap for service types in Kubernetes.</description></item><item><title>Kubernetes Homelab with K3S and Raspberry Pi 4</title><link>https://homeautomation.wiki/post/k3s-the-hard-way/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://homeautomation.wiki/post/k3s-the-hard-way/</guid><description>Building A Kubernetes Homelab with K3S and Raspberry Pi 4: The Hard Way K3S is one of the best solutions available if you want to deploy your own Kubernetes cluster inside your homelab to play with, or just for learning purposes. And it is really easy to get started with a couple of (actually, you only need one) Raspberry PIs. But &amp;ldquo;What is K3S?&amp;rdquo;, you might ask.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://homeautomation.wiki/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://homeautomation.wiki/about/</guid><description>And God said, &amp;ldquo;Let there be light,&amp;rdquo; I am not a firm believer of god but I always want to use this quote, especially when I work on something related to Linux or computers in general. Using Linux is in fact like being a god, a god who mounts disks, a god who send its petty users to /dev/null and a god who sees and who deletes.</description></item></channel></rss>